<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Student Discount Locator</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string
        name="action_settings">Info
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_return">ReturnActivity</string>

    <string
        name="welcome_msg"
        >Hello and welcome to the\nStudent Discount Locator!
        \nTo search for discounts press the Search Button.
        \nTo submit a new discount press the Submit Button.
    </string>

    <string
        name="title_activity_category">CategoryActivity
    </string>
    <string
        name="category_hint">Use the menu to choose what kinds of discounts you want!
    </string>

    <string
        name="title_activity_results_map">ResultsMap
    </string>
    <string
        name="title_activity_submit">SubmitActivity
    </string>

    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_google_place">GooglePlace</string>
    <string name="title_activity_data_port">DataPort</string>
    <string name="title_activity_google_play_services">GooglePlayServicesActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_results_detail">resultsDetail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_terms">TermsActivity</string>

    <string
        name="terms"
        >Hey there! It looks like this is your first time using Student Discount Locator
        so there are a few things we need to go over.\n\nPurpose:\nThis app is intended
        to help users save money by storing and retrieving discounts based on location.
        To do this, the app requires access to location and the ability to store data.\n
        Location is used to determine what discounts are near you and where any submitted
        discounts are located. This info is only used for the aforementioned purposes and
        is not stored or sold.\nThe data stored on your phone consists of whether you have
        seen this page and a "score" to determine value of submissions.\n\nAbout Us:\nWe
        are a group of students from Grand Valley State University\'s Android development
        course. This app is our final project and is meant to showcase the skills we learned.
        We receive no financial gains from the app and will never charge users. This app will
        be periodically updated as we become aware of issues and desired improvements.\n\n
        Legal Terms:\nBy using Student Discount Locator you agree to:\n1. not submit false or
        misleading information,\n2. not hold us liable for any false submissions of other users.
        \n\nThank you for trying Student Discount Locator!\nPress the back button to get started.
    </string>

</resources>
